- STAND BY
- ALL GOOD
- 2...
- CAN I PLAY THE 2, OR?
- HEY, CAN WE ALL...
- 2, 3, 4
♪♪♪
- MAGNIFICENT, MAGNIFICENT!
- BEAUTIFUL
[JOHN SCATS]
- BEAUTIFUL!
♪♪♪
- MAGNIFICENT,
A PERFECT RENDITION.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN
THERE YOU SEE THE GREATEST
TEAROOM ORCHESTRA IN THE WORLD.
IT'S MY PLEASURE TO INTRODUCE
NOW IN THEIR FIRST
LIVE APPEARANCE
FOR GOODNESS KNOWS HOW LONG
IN FRONT OF AN AUDIENCE,
THE BEATLES.
♪ IT'S NOW OR NEVER! ♪
♪♪♪
♪ HEY JUDE ♪
♪ HEY JUDE, DON'T MAKE IT BAD ♪
♪ TAKE A SAD SONG
AND MAKE IT BETTER ♪
♪ REMEMBER TO LET HER
INTO YOUR HEART ♪
♪ THEN YOU CAN START
TO MAKE IT BETTER ♪
♪ HEY JUDE, DON'T BE AFRAID ♪
♪ YOU WERE MADE TO
GO OUT AND GET HER ♪
♪ THE MINUTE (OHHHH) ♪
♪ YOU LET HER UNDER YOUR SKIN
(OHHHH) ♪
♪ THEN YOU BEGIN
TO MAKE IT BETTER ♪
♪ AND ANYTIME YOU FEEL THE PAIN
(OHHHH) ♪
♪ HEY JUDE, REFRAIN,
DON'T CARRY THE WORLD
UPON YOUR SHOULDERS ♪
♪ FOR WELL YOU KNOW
THAT IT'S A FOOL (OHHHH) ♪
♪ WHO PLAYS IT COOL,
BY MAKING HIS WORLD
A LITTLE COLDER ♪
♪ NA NA NA NA NA
NA NA NA NA NA ♪
♪ HEY JUDE, DON'T LET ME DOWN ♪
♪ YOU HAVE FOUND HER,
NOW GO AND GET HER ♪
♪ REMEMBER TO LET HER
INTO YOUR HEART (OHHHH) ♪
♪ THEN YOU CAN START
TO MAKE IT BETTER ♪
- YEAH!
♪ SO LET IT OUT AND LET IT IN,
HEY JUDE, BEGIN ♪
♪ YOU'RE WAITING FOR SOMEONE
TO PERFORM WITH ♪
♪ AND DON'T YOU KNOW
THAT IT'S JUST YOU,
HEY JUDE, YOU'LL DO ♪
♪ THE MOVEMENT YOU NEED
IS ON YOUR SHOULDER ♪
♪ NA NA NA NA NA NA NA NA,
YEAH ♪
♪ HEY JUDE, DON'T MAKE IT BAD ♪
♪ TAKE A SAD SONG
AND MAKE IT BETTER ♪
♪ REMEMBER TO LET HER
UNDER YOUR SKIN ♪
♪ THEN YOU'LL BEGIN TO MAKE IT ♪
♪ BETTER, BETTER, BETTER,
BETTER, BETTER, BETTER, OH ♪
♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH,
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH
(NAA NA NA NA, NA NA NA NA) ♪
♪ NA NA NA NA, HEY JUDE ♪
♪ NAA NA NA NA NA NA NA,
NA NA NA NA, HEY JUDE ♪
♪ (JUDE, JUDY, JUDY,
JUDY, JUDY, JUDY, YEAH) ♪
♪ NAA NA NA NA NA NA NA
NA NA NA NA, HEY JUDE ♪
[VOCALIZING]
♪ (COME ON AND BRING ME JUDY) ♪
[CLAPPING]
♪ NAA NA NA NA NA NA NA
(YEAH YEAH YEAH),
NA NA NA NA, HEY JUDE ♪
♪ (YOU KNOW YOU CAN MAKE,
JUDE JUDE, YOU'RE NOT
GONNA BREAK IT) ♪
♪ NAA NA NA NA NA NA NA,
NA NA NA NA, HEY JUDE ♪
[VOCALIZING]
♪ NAA NA NA NA NA NA NA,
NA NA NA NA, HEY JUDE ♪
[CLAPPING INTENSIFIES]
♪ NAA NA NA NA NA NA NA,
(OH YEAH) NA NA NA NA,
HEY JUDE ♪
♪ NAA NA NA NA NA NA NA,
(TAKE A LOAD OFF, JUDY)
NA NA NA NA, HEY JUDE ♪
♪ (TAKE A LOAD OFF BABY) ♪
[VOCALIZING]
♪ NAA NA NA NA NA NA NA,
(YEAH, YEAH, YEAH)
NA NA NA NA, HEY JUDE (YEAH!) ♪
♪ NAA NA NA NA NA NA NA,
NA NA NA NA, HEY JUDE ♪
♪ (YEAH, YEAH, YEAH) ♪
♪ NAA NA NA NA NA NA NA
NA NA NA NA, HEY JUDE
(YEAH, YEAH, YEAH!) ♪
♪ NAA NA NA NA NA NA NA,
NA NA NA NA, HEY JUDE ♪